每一个建筑师都有一件拿的出手的杰作\n这是他们职业的辉煌转折点
Every architect can point to that\none design that changed their career.
对于我来说 \n是在31岁的生日创造出的杰作
For me,it was around the\ntime of my 31st birthday.
它既不是博物馆 音乐厅 也不是摩天楼
It wasn't a museum or a\nconcert hall or a skyscraper.
是别的建筑
It was something else.
我们要开一家叫肋骨城的餐厅\n最好它的形状是...
We're opening a restaurant called Rib\nTown,and we want it to be shaped...
像一顶牛仔帽
Like a cowboy hat.
听着 我需要这份工作
Look,I need the work.
我别无选择啊
I don't have any other options.
嗯 还可以去教课嘛
Well,there's always that teaching job.
哼 我累死累活得才不是为了去教书呢\n逊毙了还没前途
Yeah,I didn't work this hard toe stuck\nin some crappy,dead-end teaching job.
绝无冒犯之意 Lily
No offense,Lily.
我今天被小孩淋尿了三次\n不想再争论什么了
I got peed on three times\ntoday. No arguments here.
我要专心设计这间牛仔帽餐厅去了\n三天后见吧
I just gotta nail this hat building\nso,I'll see you all in three days.
接下来三天 \n我非常非常认真得投入到设计工作中去
For the next three days,I worked\nharder than I'd ever worked in my life.
却是... 毫无进展
And I got... nowhere.
嘿 Ted 在干嘛呢?
Hey,Ted,whatcha doing?
设计一间帽子形状的餐厅
Designing a building shaped like a hat.
- 所以现在不适合聊天咯?\n- 不适合
- Now a good time to chat?\n- No.
你觉得Robin怎么样?
So,what do you think of Robin?
Barney 我要开始工作了 所以...
Barney,I really need\nto get to work,so...
好吧 假设咱们在买西装
Great.Say you and I went suit-shopping,
你看中了其中一件\n一件很不错的加拿大西装
and you happened upon a beautiful\nsuit,a beautiful Canadian suit.
双排扣的
Double-breasted.
你试了试 觉得并不合身
You try it on,but it's not\nexactly the right fit for you.
于是你放回去了 然后我试了下
So,you put it back. Then I try it on.
我并不想买你看上的同一款西装
I don't really want to take the\nsame suit that you had your eye on,
但是这次 我是真的很喜欢这款
but at the same time,I\nreally like that suit.
去买吧 Barney \n显然你真的很喜欢它
Buy the suit,Barney. You\nclearly care about it.
告诉这件西装你的真实感受吧
Tell the suit how you feel.
好的
Okay.
但是Ted 记得这可是你说的 因为..
But Ted,remember that that\nwas your answer because...
这件西装就是Robin 我就知道!
The suit is Robin. I know!
对吧?
Right?
- 我支持你 伙计 \n- 你现在当然这样说
- I'm with you,buddy.\n- You are now.
因为我跟你挑明了
Because I explained it to you.
老爸老妈浪漫史\n第四季 第24集
How I Met Your\nMother Season04 Episode24
好了 伙计 \n三天来你都昼夜不停得扑在这个设计上
Come on,dude,you've been at this\nfor three days without a break.
今天是你的生日
Now,it's your birthday.
跟我到屋顶上喝啤酒吧
Come up to the roof\nand have a beer with me.
不行 明天就要演示设计了
No can do. Presentation is tomorrow.
帽子餐厅的设计图可不会自动蹦出来
Hat buildings don't design themselves.
这是为肥胖游客设计的肋骨餐厅
It's a rib joint for fat tourists.
只要把门弄宽些 椅子结实点就行了
Just make sure the doors are wide\nand the chairs are reinforced.
好了 去屋顶喝庆生啤酒吧 走咯!
Now,birthday beer on the roof. Let's go!
你为啥那么想让我到屋顶去?
Why do you want me to\ncome up to the roof so bad?
干嘛 想给我一个惊喜的派对啊?
What,are you throwing\nme a surprise party?
什么? \nTed 去年我们给你搞了个惊喜派对
What? Ted,we threw you a\nsurprise party last year.
不可能连续两年给你弄这个的
Okay,you don't get two\nsurpse parties in a row.
大家赏脸参加第一个派对就已经够惊喜了 对吧?
I mean,the fact that anyone showed up at\nthe first one was surprise enough,right?
连续两年办惊喜派对!
Two surprise parties in a row!
太有聊了! 太有聊了!
That is rich! That is rich!
太经典了! 他还是不肯上来
Classic! He still won't come up.
够了 怎么回事啊?
Come on. What the crap?
我就说办第二次惊喜派对是个馊主意
I knew having a second\nsurprise party was a bad idea.
是的 Robin 我知道了
Yes,Robin,I know.
这个派对真是... 真是场灾难\n这是我出的主意
This party is... it's a\ndisaster. It was my idea.
我来负责任
I take responsibility.
只能这样做来弥补了
And there's really only\none thing to do about it.
- 哦 Marshall 不要啊 \n- Lily 我一定要做!
- Oh,Marshall,no.\n- Lily,I have to do this!
这次什么也阻止不了我了
No point in putting it off any longer.
我要解释一下
I should explain.
你们瞧 几年前...
You see,a few years earlier...
不 算了吧 这玩意一点也不潮
No,uh-uh,forget it. This\nis so not pimped out.
或者说 逊毙了
If anything,this is pimped in.
你知道谁最会生活吗? 那些家伙
You know who knows how\nto live? Those people.
说得是对面楼的天井
Ah,the rooftop patio one\nbuilding over from ours.
跨越不过六七英尺鸿沟便可到达园林天堂
Across a chasm of just six or seven\nfeet awaited a landscaped paradise.
最美好的是...
And best of all...
那个浴池看着真棒
That looks to be one hot tub.
很好 咱们怎么过去呢?
Great. How do we get over there?
我们怎么办呢? 跳过去?
What are we gonna do? Jump?
我可以跳得过去
I can jump that far.
Marshall
你最近从沙发上跳下来都得跳个两回了
Marshall,lately it takes you\ntwo tries to get off the sofa.
你跳不过去的
You can't jump that far.
- 真的?\n- 真的
- Really?\n- Really.
看我的
Watch me.
但是他没跳
But he didn't jump.
1小时后
******
这个泡着其实也不赖
This actually is kind of nice.
对吧? 对吧?
Right? Right?
好的...
Okay...
接下来几年 他都是处于预备跳的状态
And in the years that\nfollowed,he kept almost jumping.
好了... 好了!
Okay... Okay!
但是每一次 毫无悬念的...
But each time,without fail...
好了 我跳了
Okay. Here we go.
他都没跳成
He didn't jump.
请别担心
But don't worry.
如果我今晚跳过去了\n就还是能保住这个"惊喜"派对
'Cause if I can make this jump\ntonight,it's totally gonna save the party.
亲爱的 求你下来吧
Honey,please get down from there.
Lily 当飞车英雄Evel Knievel\n在蛇河峡谷边缘跨上他的星条旗战车
Lily,when Evel Knievel sat astride his star-spangled\nrocket on the rim of Snake River Canyon,
你觉得他的老婆会说"亲爱的 你下来吧'吗?
do you think his wife\nsaid,Honey,get down from there?
最后再说一次 我不是Linda Knievel!
For the last time,I\nam not Linda Knievel!
我也不可能成为Linda Knievel!
I will never be Linda Knievel!
你不需要提醒我
You don't need to remind me.
Marshall 求你别这样 别跳
Marshall,please don't do this.
Lily 我非跳不可
Lily,but I gotta do this.
- 你不能这样做 \n- 为什么?
- You can't do this.\n- Why?
你想听理由? 那我就告诉你\n我怀孕了
You want a reason? I'll give\nyou a reason. I'm pregnant.
哦 天啊!
Oh,my God!
哦 天啊 真的吗?
Oh,my God,really?
Lily 我确实是觉得你最近胖了不少
Lily,I mean,I noticed that you\ngained some weight lately...
我骗你的 猪头!
I was lying,you jerk!
尽管去跳吧 我巴不得你死了算了!
Oh,go ahead and jump. I hope you die!
这算是同意了咯
That's all the permission I need.
听着 Robin...
Listen,Robin...
- 我有话对你说 \n- 等等
- There's something I have to tell you.\n- But wait.
这你说之前 我也有话要说
Before you do,I have to\ntell you something first.
说什么?
What is it?
我想我爱上你了
I think I'm in love with you.
是Ted 大家别出声!
It's Ted. Everybody shh!
嘿 Ted 怎么了?
Hey,Ted,what's up?
它在这儿 Lily
It's here,Lily.
它在盯着我看
It's looking at me.
什么东西?
What is?
那只山羊
The goat.
我已经跟你们提过山羊的事了
Now,I've told you some of\nthe story of the goat already.
你们的Lily阿姨曾邀请一位当地的农民去班里\n他还带来一头山羊
How Aunt Lily invited a local farmer to come\ntalk to her class,and how he brought a goat,
他告诉班里的小朋友 \n接下来怎么处置这头羊
and how he told the whole class what he\nwas gonna do to the goat later that day.
然后Lily阿姨出于善心 买下了这头羊\n让它免于一死
And how Aunt Lily,in a fit of mercy,bought the\ngoat off the guy in order to commute its sentence.
Lily 奇迹发生了
Lily,something amazing has happened.
我刚跟Robin聊天 \n我准备告诉她对她的感觉
I was talking to Robin,I was\nall set to tell her how I feel,
但在我开口之前 \n你都不会相信她先说了什么
but before I could,you'll\nnev believe what she said.
我想我爱上你了
I think I'm in love with you.
你怎么回答的?
What did you say?
你想我还能怎么说呢? \n遇到这样的事还能说什么呢?
What do you think I said? What would\nanyone say to something like that?
好吧... Robin 听着
Yeah... Robin,listen.
你很好 很优秀 但是我的意思是\n咱俩是朋友
You're great. I mean,you're really\nawesome,but I mean,we're friends.
这可不是个好主意
It's probably a bad idea.
我想你说的没错
I-I guess you're right.
哦 祝你玩得愉快
Uh,have a good party.
你也是 小鬼
You too,kiddo.
什么?
What?
她一开口 我立马没感觉了
It's like,as soon as she\nsaid that,no more feelings.
我再也不爱她了
I'm not in love with her anymore.
你爱这个女孩一年多
So,you've been in love with\nthis girl for the past year,
在她对你生情 倾吐爱意的那一刻 \n你立刻对她没感觉了
and the second she reciprocates those\nfeelings,just like that,you're over her.
这感觉多棒啊!
How great is that?
不! 不! 这是条毛巾 不是吃的
No! No! This is a washcloth. Not food.
搞什么...
What the...
好了... 就是这样
Okay... this is it.
我要... 跳了!
Here we... Go!
就这样
This is it.
Tracey Tracey
告诉Lily你刚跟我说什么了
Tracey,Tracey,tell Lily\nwhat you just told me.
我刚搬来纽约?
Um,that I just moved to New York?
不 不 在这之前的事
No,no,but tell her how you got here.
我从衣阿华州来 刚下车
I just got off the bus from Iowa.
从衣阿华州来 刚下车!
Just got off the bus from Iowa!
这样一位天才舞蹈家 真是幸运
How lucky is it that an aspiring dancer
她从衣阿华州来 才刚下车\n就遇到了Rockettes舞蹈公司的制作人
just off the bus from Iowa runs\ninto the producer of the Rockettes?
我觉得就像在演经典舞蹈剧一样
I feel like I'm in one of\nthose classic show biz stories.
哦 亲爱的 你确实是在剧里
Oh,honey,you are. You really are.
嘿 Tracey 为\n何不给我调点你老爹喜欢喝的朗姆酒混啤酒?
Hey,Tracey,why don't you make me one of those\nrum and beers that your dad loves so much?
当然可以啦!
Sure thing!
- 该死\n- 什么?
- Damn it.\n- What?
大家都说不要告诉Lily
Everybody always says,Don't tell Lily.
Lily守不住秘密\n通常 他们说的没错
Lily can't keep a secret.\nAnd,usually,they're right.
但这次 我忍住没说
But this time,I kept the secret.
然后你跑来我面前来了这么一段\n逼我回复我Lily的本性
And then you come along with this crap and\nyou force me to pull an old classic Lily
只能泄密了!\n(原意为撒豆)
and spill the beans!
有啥豆子? 还有豆子呢?
What beans? There's beans?
秘密是这样来的
There's beans.
这件西装就是Robin
The suit is Robin.
我就知道! 对吧?
I know! Right?
我支持你 伙计
I'm with you,buddy.
你现在当然会啦
You are now.
因为我跟你挑明了
Because I explained it to you.
乖
There you go.
哦 惨了
Oh,crap.
他那么说的? 老天爷啊!
He said that? Oh,my God!
简直是空前绝后的大惊喜啊!
What a tremendous\nground-breaking surprise!
- 你知道多久了?\n- 8个月
- How long have you known?\n- Eight months.
你保密了那么久? 不容易啊
And you've kept it a secret\nsince then? Good for you.
是啊 难得啊 Lily
Yeah. Good for you,Lily.
好惊人 谁预料到了?
I mean,what a bombshell.\nWho saw that coming?
- 你知道多久了?\n- 7个月29天
- How long have you known?\n- Seven months,29 days.
天啊 我该怎么办?
God,what am I going to do?
我不知道 你打算怎么办?
I don't know. What are you going to do?
我要在教堂里跟Barney结婚
I'm going to marry Barney\nin a big church wedding.
然后搬到新罕布什尔州的某个浪漫小镇 \n经营家小旅馆
And we're going to move to some sleepy New\nHampshire town and open a bed-and-breakfast.
- 啊 真的吗?\n- 当然不是!
- Aww,really?\n- No!
那是Barney 我是说...
It's Barney. I mean...
是Barney 但那是Barney啊
it's Barney. But it's Barney.
我要拒绝他
I got to tell him no.
乖乖 这会伤了他的那个...
Oh,man,you're going to break his...
那个泵血的小黑心的
Whatever it is that pumps that\nblack sludge through his veins.
该死 你说的对
Crap. You're right.
Barney首次表白就被拒
The first time Barney expresses\nfeelings for a girl and she rejects him?
还不是被普通女孩拒绝 我是说...
And not just any girl. I mean...
这会让他崩溃的
It will destroy him.
好吧 首先...
Okay,well,first of all...
其次还有个变通之策 高风险 高回报
Second of all,there is a maneuver you can\ntry. It's high-risk,but it's also high-reward.
没有啥专业命名 我就叫他...
For lack of a better\nterm,I'm going to call it...
莫斯比法则\n(Ted的姓)
The Mosby.
- 莫斯比法则?\n- 不 她不能莫斯比了他
- The Mosby?\n- No,she couldn't Mosby him.
她绝对能把他莫斯比了
She could Mosby the crap out of him.
莫斯比啥意思?
What's the Mosby?
Robin 还记得你跟Ted的首次约会吗?
Robin,you remember your\nfirst date with Ted?
你都想跳上电车 直奔闹市了
You wanted to hop on the\nT-train and take a ride downtown.
我都准备好跳过转门了
I was ready to jump that turnstile.
为什么会这样的呢?
What changed all that?
- 我好像爱上你了\n- 什么?
- I think I'in love with you.\n- What?
这就是莫斯比!
The Mosby!
太有才了 还有... 拜托哦
That is genius. And,um... excuse me.
我知道你很美\n但你太高了 还不相信有鬼
I mean,you're very pretty,but you're\nfreakishly tall,and you don't believe in ghosts.
所以她说爱上我了 其实正相反
So,when she said she thinks she's in\nlove with me,she meant the opposite.
没错 你看多管用 你都回归正常了
Exactly. And look how well it\nworked. You're back to normal.
是啊 没错
Yes. Yes,I am.
太牛了 太帅了
And it is great. It's awesome.
- 所以Robin并不爱我\n- 没错
- So,Robin's not in love with me.\n- Nope.
为什么不爱嘛?
Why not?
山羊先生?
Mr. Goat?
好了 到这里吧
Okay. That's it.
笨山羊
Stupid goat.
你怎么就迷恋上这条毛巾了呢
I do not understand your\nfascination with this washcloth.
都怪你脑仁就这么点大...
I guess at's what happen when\nyou have a brain thsize of a...
表 表 表!
No,no,no!
好了 好了 好了...
Okay,okay,okay...
Marshall 你能去叫Ted吗?
Hey,Marshall,can you just go get Ted?
Lily 我-刚-要-跳-的
Lily,I was just about to jump.
没看我一直重复"好了"吗?
Didn't you hear me saying\n"Okay" over and over again?
哦 对不起 你快跳
Oh,I'm sorry. Go ahead and jump.
不 算了吧 对不起大伙 Lily拦着我
No,it's fine. Sorry,everybody.\nLily won't let me jump.
是啊
Yeah.
感谢上帝
Thank God.
快打120!
Hospital!
到底发生了什么?
So,what happened exactly?
发生了你私放野兽入室事件
What happened is you let a freaking\nwild animal into our apartment.
它对我很暴力
I was savaged.
这是全世界最耐人的小山羊了
That is the sweetest,cutest\nlittle goat in the whole world.
全世界最耐人的小山羊?
Sweetest,cutest little\ngoat in the whole world?
我那时很缺乏睡眠
I was prettyleep-deprived\nat this point,
所以可能记不住事 但我记得是...
so this probably isn't how it really\nhappened,but here's how I remember it.
你就是那个想上山羊的人?
So,you're the guy who tried\nto make it with a goat?
嘿 就算是上 也是那只山羊想上我
Hey,if anything,that goat\ntried to make it with me.
- 我能离开吗?\n- 当然可以
- Can I go,please?\n- Sure,you can go.
不过记住哦 "^"的意思是"别"哦
But remember,buddy,"baa" means "baa."
这下好了 我的设计演示要迟到了
Great. Great. Now I'm going\nto be late for my presentation.
多亏山羊先生
Thanks a lot,Mr. Goat.
山羊先生? Ted 那是母羊 叫Missy
Mr. Goat? Ted,that goat's\na girl. Her name's Missy.
你被女生打倒了
You got beat up by a girl.
- 所以你爱上我了\n- 什么?
- So. You're in love with me.\n- What?
哦对 特别爱你
Oh,yeah. Very much.
好了 别装了 Lily都告诉我了
Okay,you can knock it off. Lily told me.
该死的 Lily!
Damn it. Lily!
不敢相信你会这么做
I can't believe you would do that.
这是因为我关心你 Barney
It's just... Like,I care\nabout you,Barney. And...
这些事 这些情感的事?
This kind of stuff,the emotional stuff?
你不在行 我以为我是帮你摆脱麻烦呢
It's not your thing. I thought\nI'd save you the trouble.
也许我不想摆脱麻烦呢
Well,maybe I don't want\nto be saved the trouble.
也许我就想要麻烦呢
Maybe I want the trouble.
一直以来我都不想有这些麻烦
I haven't wanted the\ntrouble in a long time.
但是跟你在一起 麻烦好像不麻烦了
But with you,the trouble\ndoesn't seem so. troubling.
不知道 我以为...
I don't know. I thought...
我以为你也会这么想
I guess I thought you felt the se way.
也许我就这么想 我也不知道
Maybe I do. I don't know.
我不善于直面感情
I'm not exactly the biggest\nconfronter of feelings.
显然 咱俩之间有点火花
I mean,clearly,there's\nsomething between us.
我大脑想着要把它扼杀在摇篮里\n就因为我心里另有所想
Maybe my head was saying,"Nip it in the bud"\nbecause my heart was saying something else.
听着... 我确实对你有感觉 Barney
Look... I have feelings for you,Barney.
也许甚至爱上了你
Maybe I even love you.
- 哎哟 进展太快了吧? 你不觉得咩\n- 什么?
- This is going pretty fast,don't you think?\n- What?
咱俩现在是好朋友
We have a really good friendship going.
为什么要毁掉这段关系?
Why screw up a good thing?
- 做朋友?\n- 做朋友
- Friends?\n- Friends.
娘啊 你又来了 你又莫斯比了我
Oh,my God. You just did it\nagain. You just Mosby'd me.
- 我没有\n- 就有 你好狡猾
- I did not.\n- You did. You little minx.
好吧 你说对了 我刚还是莫斯比
Okay,you're right. I did just Mosby you.
为什么不给咱俩一个机会?
Why are you so afraid\nof giving this a chance?
因为我担心自己喜欢你太深
Because I am scared\nof how much I like you.
哇噢 这可不是好主意
Whoa,this is a bad idea.
没错 这是个错误
You're right. This is a mistake.
- 没错 错了\n- 我爱你
- Yes. No.\n- I love you.
- 咱做朋友吧\n- 好吧 那就朋友
- Let's be friends.\n- Okay,friends,then.
- 我爱你\n- 咱结婚吧
- I love you.\n- Let's get married.
- 不 你别逼我\n- 好吧 那算了
- No,you're smothering me.\n- Okay,forget it.
其实我们以后再讨论这个
You know what? We can\nsort this out later.
- 是啊 好主意\n- 听上去不错
- Yeah,that sounds good.\n- That sounds good.
那是疯狂漫长的一夜 但转天早晨
It had been a long and\ncrazy night,but that morning,
抛开琐事 我成功进行了展示
against all odds,I made\nit to my presentation.
先生们 这就是了 肋骨城
Here you have it,gentlemen. Rib Town.
是不是? 好吧?
Right? Right?
是啊
Yeah.
Ted 听我说 你很牛...
Ted,listen. You're great,and\nyou've done a real...
做的也很好 有天定会让别的餐馆满意的
special job here,and you're going to make\nsome other restaurant very happy someday,
但我们决定...
but,uh,we have,uh,decided to go...
- 选另一个风格\n- 什么?
- another direction here.\n- What?
你看好了哦...
Feast your eyes on...
- 肋骨城!\n- 肋骨城!
- Rib Town!\n- Rib Town!
Sven
(怪兽喷火银行设计组)
Sven.
我跟你说
I'll tell you one thing.
我再也不吃肋骨了
I'm never eating ribs again.
才怪
Yeah,right.
爷再也...不吃...肋骨了!
I am never... eating ribs... again!
不在Ted面前吃了!
In front of Ted!
真是梦魇啊
This is a disaster.
我要怎么重新振作起来?
How am I going to come back from this?
好吧 我想问句
Okay,I'm just going to ask this.
你真的想重新再来吗?
Do you really want to\ncome back from this?
你什么意思?
What's that supposed to mean?
建筑业快毁掉你了 Ted\n我们都看不下去了
Architecture is killing you,Ted,and\nit's killing us to watch it killing you.
你就像山羊看上了毛巾
You're like that goat\nwith the washcloth.
你太想要了 别人越拦你 你越要抢
You want it so bad,and every time the world tries\nto take it away from you,you keep grabbing it.
要知道不过是毛巾而已 干嘛这么想要?
But you know what? It's just a\nwashcloth. Why do you even want it?
因为...我要当建筑师
Because I... I have to\nbe an architect. That's...
我这么计划的
that's the plan.
让计划去死吧 我计划当知名艺术家的
Screw the plan. I planned\non being a famous artist.
Marshall计划当环境法律师
Marshall planned on being\nan environmental lawyer.
Robin计划当电视名嘴的
Robin planned on being a TV reporter.
我计划成真了啊 早晨4点档都是我的
I am a TV reporter. I'm on\nevery morning at 4:00 a.m.
还在播啊 好事好事
Is that still on? Oh,good for you.
拜托 还是有人看的
Somebody watch it,please.
Barney计划做小提琴家的
Barney planned on being a violinist.
- Lily
- 啥也别说了
- Lily.\n- Don't tell me things.
你不能像设计建筑一样设计生活
Look,you can't design\nyour life like a building.
日子不是这么过的
It doesn't work that way.
你好好生活 生活会自己规划的
You just have to live\nit,and it will design itself.
那我啥都不做吗?
So,what,I should just do nothing?
不是 要听人劝 大胆飞跃
No. Listen to what the world is\ntelling you to do and take the leap.
你是对的 你说的很对
You're right. You're absolutely right.
我爱你 Lily
I love you,Lily.
哎呀 跳跃是个比喻 是个比喻!
Oh,no. Metaphorical\nleap. Metaphorical leap!
- 这可不好玩\n- 别啊
- This is not cool.\n- Don't do it.
不要!
No!
- 我成功了!\n- 宝贝 你成功了
- I did it!\n- Baby,you did it.
- 我无所不能!\n- 没错的
- I can do anything!\n- Yes,you can.
我要去买摩托车!
I'm getting a motorcycle!
- 你别做梦了!\n- 好吧 对不起 大家都过来啊
- You absolutely are not!\n- Okay,sorry. Guys,me on over.
今年我在婚礼上被甩了
That was the year I\ngot left at the altar.
今年我被酒吧男招待揍了
It was the year I got knocked\nout by a crazy bartender.
今年我被炒了
The year I got fired.
今年我被山羊击败了
The year I got beat up by a goat.
还是只母的
A girl goat,at that.
不过今年可真是好年头
And damn it if it wasn't\nthe best year of my life.
因为如果上述事情没发生
Because,if any one of those\nthings hadn't happened,
我就不会得到这最好的工作
I never would have ended up in a which\nturned out to be the best job I ever had.
最重要的是 我也不会见到你们的妈妈了
But more importantly,I\nwouldn't have met your mother,
因为你知道...她也在班上
because,as you know...she\nwas in that class.
而且 故事才刚刚开始\n(期待下一季Barney和Robin的浪漫吧)
But of course,that story\nis only just beginning.